The air is thin, my head is tight Beneath the
sharp and western light A ghost inside this
diesel drone
A thousand miles still all alone
The mountain peaks, a jagged crown
In this cold and mile-high town Just wanna drink
a piece of breath But there's a voice inside my
head A mile high, but I'm sinking low A silent no
is all I know My stomach's empty, throat is dry
Beneath the cold Colorado sky And there's a
whisper of a different pain A secret fire, a
burning stain I can't say a word, she'll never
see The pieces that are breaking inside me
Another station, another crowd
Her angry sighs are getting loud
We change the bus a hurried pace
No kindness in this bitter place
I watch the others free to go A life I'll never get
to know Just bite my tongue and play the part
And hide the panic in my heart A mile high, but I'm
sinking low A silent no is all I know My stomach's
empty, throat is dry Beneath the cold Colorado
sky And there's a whisper of a different pain A
secret fire, a burning stain I can't say a word,
she'll never see The pieces that are breaking
inside me
I'm
A mile high, but I'm sinking low A silent no is all
I know My stomach's empty, throat is dry Beneath
a cold Colorado sky And there's a whisper of a
different pain A secret fire, a burning stain I
can't say a word, she'll never see The pieces
that are breaking inside
you